<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><FastLanePlus UploaderID="18243007" AgentID="" Version="3.0">
					  <Client ID="18243007" MinJobs="0" MaxJobs="9999999"><Job Reference="61243000000235895" TemplateID="83291" ScreenID="">
						      <Title>Catering Assistants and Weekend Cooks</Title>
						      <SearchTitle>Catering Assistants and Weekend Cooks</SearchTitle>
						      <Description>Cater Care Australia specialises in providing catering services to sectors such as Retail – Coffee Shops, Health &amp; Juice Bars, Business and Industry - Industrial Canteens, Healthcare - Nursing Homes, Retirement Villages and Education - Private Schools, Universities and TAFE Colleges.</Description>
						      <AdDetails><![CDATA[Cater Care Australia specialises in providing catering services to sectors such as Retail – Coffee Shops, Health &amp; Juice Bars, Business and Industry - Industrial Canteens, Healthcare - Nursing Homes, Retirement Villages and Education - Private Schools, Universities and TAFE Colleges. Our core values of Care, Pride and Community are values that our people own and believe in, and demonstrate throughout all aspects of our business, on a daily basis. 


<br />• Dynamic and Fast Growing Company
<br />•	Various locations in Queensland
<br />•	Casual Position

<br />We are currently seeking the services of Catering Assistants and Weekend Cooks in casual positions to join our site based teams in various locations around Queensland.

The Catering Assistant and Weekend Cook will be responsible for:  
<br />•	Driving the Cater Care core values; 
<br />•	Ensuring effective operation of the food preparation, production and service requirements of your site.


<br />You will be required to adhere to catering standards as set by the Company which incorporate cooking methods and food presentation.  You will have strong work ethics combined with time management skills and will be prepared to assist other kitchen staff in maintaining cleaning schedules and service commitments when required.


The successful applicants will have the following skills and experience:

<br />•	A passion for excellent customer services skills with the ability to be flexible
<br />•	Motivated and accountable
<br />•	Relevant industry experience
<br />•	Demonstrated experience in Safety and HACCP


<br />Experience with a similar role in a contract catering environment will be highly regarded. To apply for this position please send a resume in word format to petert@catercareaustralia.com.au or by fax on (07) 33973988]]></AdDetails>
						      <ApplicationEmail>leon@catercareservices.com.au</ApplicationEmail>
						      <ApplicationURL>http://www.catercare.com.au/career/?jobid=61243000000235895</ApplicationURL>
						      <ResidentsOnly>Yes</ResidentsOnly>
						      <Items>
						        <Item Name="Jobtitle">Catering Assistants and Weekend Cooks</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant">CHARMAINE SPARROW (0855SPAC)</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Email">leon@catercareservices.com.au</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Telephone">1300 658 700</Item>
						        <Item Name="RefNumber">61243000000235895</Item>
						      </Items>
						      <Listing MarketSegments="Main">
							        <Classification Name="Location">Brisbane</Classification>
							        <Classification Name="Area"></Classification>
							        <Classification Name="WorkType">CasualVacation</Classification>
							       	<Classification Name="Classification">HospitalityTourism</Classification>
						        	<Classification Name="SubClassification">Kitchen &amp; Sandwich Hands</Classification>					      
						      </Listing>
						      <Salary Type="AnnualPackage" Min="1" Max="39999" AdditionalText="" />
						      <StandOut IsStandOut="false" LogoID="172084" Bullet1="" Bullet2="" Bullet3="" />
						    </Job>
						<Job Reference="61243000000235919" TemplateID="83291" ScreenID="">
						      <Title>Catering Assistants</Title>
						      <SearchTitle>Catering Assistants</SearchTitle>
						      <Description>Cater Care Australia specialises in providing catering services to sectors such as Retail – Coffee Shops, Health &amp; Juice Bars, Business and Industry - Industrial Canteens, Healthcare - Nursing Homes, Retirement Villages and Education - Private Schools, Universities and TAFE Colleges.</Description>
						      <AdDetails><![CDATA[Cater Care Australia specialises in providing catering services to sectors such as Retail – Coffee Shops, Health &amp; Juice Bars, Business and Industry - Industrial Canteens, Healthcare - Nursing Homes, Retirement Villages and Education - Private Schools, Universities and TAFE Colleges.  Our core values of Care, Pride and Community are values that our people own and believe in, and demonstrate throughout all aspects of our business, on a daily basis.

<br />•	Adelaide Metro Area
<br />•	Casual position
<br />•	Available with varying hours

<br />We are currently seeking the services of an experienced Catering Assistant to be part of our site team based in Adelaide Metro Area. 

The Catering Assistant role will be responsible for:

<br />•	Driving the Cater Care core values
<br />•	Food preparation and hygiene maintenance in accordance with Company standards and providing outstanding service to our customers along with maintaining cleanliness and the presentation standards of dining room areas.

<br />The successful applicant will have the following skills and experience:

<br />•	Exceptional customer service skills
<br />•	Enthusiastic, motivated and reliable
<br />•	Eye for detail
<br />•	Knowledge of the correct use of chemicals
<br />•	Ability to understand and comply with Material Safety Data Sheets (MSDS)
<br />•	Food handling knowledge and skills
<br />•	Food Handler’s Certificate or be willing to obtain one

<br />You will be a team player with a positive attitude who ideally will have experience with a similar role.

<br />•	Current references required at the interview
<br />•	A Police Check/Working With Children Check will be required
 
<br />To apply for this position please send a resume to r.lloyd@catercareaustralia.com.au.]]></AdDetails>
						      <ApplicationEmail>leon@catercareservices.com.au</ApplicationEmail>
						      <ApplicationURL>http://www.catercare.com.au/career/?jobid=61243000000235919</ApplicationURL>
						      <ResidentsOnly>Yes</ResidentsOnly>
						      <Items>
						        <Item Name="Jobtitle">Catering Assistants</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant">CHARMAINE SPARROW (0855SPAC)</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Email">leon@catercareservices.com.au</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Telephone">1300 658 700</Item>
						        <Item Name="RefNumber">61243000000235919</Item>
						      </Items>
						      <Listing MarketSegments="Main">
							        <Classification Name="Location">Adelaide</Classification>
							        <Classification Name="Area"></Classification>
							        <Classification Name="WorkType">CasualVacation</Classification>
							       	<Classification Name="Classification">HospitalityTourism</Classification>
						        	<Classification Name="SubClassification">Kitchen &amp; Sandwich Hands</Classification>					      
						      </Listing>
						      <Salary Type="AnnualPackage" Min="1" Max="39999" AdditionalText="" />
						      <StandOut IsStandOut="false" LogoID="172084" Bullet1="" Bullet2="" Bullet3="" />
						    </Job>
						<Job Reference="61243000000236067" TemplateID="83291" ScreenID="">
						      <Title>Senior Operations Manager</Title>
						      <SearchTitle>Senior Operations Manager</SearchTitle>
						      <Description>Cater Care Australia specialise in the provision of catering to a diverse range of clients including Aged Care, Retirement Living, Business and Industry, Educational and Retail facilities.</Description>
						      <AdDetails><![CDATA[<br />•	Fast Growing, Progressive Private Company
<br />•	Excellent Opportunity for Career Development

<br />Cater Care Australia specialise in the provision of catering to a diverse range of clients including Aged Care, Retirement Living, Business and Industry, Educational and Retail facilities.

Due to internal promotion, we are seeking a proven senior professional to work closely with the NSW State Manager in overseeing the NSW operations of this privately owned contract catering company.

The successful candidate will be proactive with an eye for detail in the control of the company&#39;s numerous and diverse catering locations.

This is an excellent opportunity to join a fast growing progressive private company with excellent opportunity for career development. Only those applicants with a proven track record in Contract Catering Management need apply.

To apply send your resume and covering letter to:

Colin Redman, Chief Operating Officer, Cater Care Australia. 
colin@catercareaustralia.com.au]]></AdDetails>
						      <ApplicationEmail>leon@catercareservices.com.au</ApplicationEmail>
						      <ApplicationURL>http://www.catercare.com.au/career/?jobid=61243000000236067</ApplicationURL>
						      <ResidentsOnly>Yes</ResidentsOnly>
						      <Items>
						        <Item Name="Jobtitle">Senior Operations Manager</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant">PETA MCDONNELL (0573MCDP)</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Email">leon@catercareservices.com.au</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Telephone">1300 658 700</Item>
						        <Item Name="RefNumber">61243000000236067</Item>
						      </Items>
						      <Listing MarketSegments="Main">
							        <Classification Name="Location">Sydney</Classification>
							        <Classification Name="Area"></Classification>
							        <Classification Name="WorkType">FullTime</Classification>
							       	<Classification Name="Classification">HospitalityTourism</Classification>
						        	<Classification Name="SubClassification">HospitalTourismManagement</Classification>					      
						      </Listing>
						      <Salary Type="AnnualPackage" Min="80000" Max="119999" AdditionalText="" />
						      <StandOut IsStandOut="false" LogoID="172084" Bullet1="" Bullet2="" Bullet3="" />
						    </Job>
						<Job Reference="61243000000233013" TemplateID="83291" ScreenID="">
						      <Title>SHE Advisor</Title>
						      <SearchTitle>SHE Advisor</SearchTitle>
						      <Description>Cater Care Services specialises in providing facility support services to the Mining, Construction, Off-Shore and Defence Industries</Description>
						      <AdDetails><![CDATA[Cater Care Services specialises in providing facility support services to the Mining, Construction, Off-Shore and Defence Industries through Australia and Overseas. We are currently seeking the services of an experienced SHE Coordinator to be part of our site team based in a remote site in Moranbah.

We are seeking the services of an experienced and self motivated industry professional to help implement and drive a positive safety culture within our site operations.

The successful applicant will possess the following key skills:

- Certificate IV in Occupational Health and Safety
- Strong leadership skills
- Strong written and verbal communication skills
- HACCP and Food Safety training/experience
- Current knowledge of legislative obligations relating to Occupational Safety and Health

The successful applicant will demonstrate:

- Experience in the remote mine site accommodation village industry
- Certificate IV in Assessment &amp; Workplace Training

Responsibilities of Position:

The role is responsible for supporting the Site Project Manager and team in the safe delivery of Accommodation and Catering services.

You will be responsible for ensuring site compliance to the company and client OHS systems and procedures.

You will assist in the delivery of tool box training and in site inductions.

Your consultative skills will enable you to provide professional advice and services to line staff regarding Safety and Health practice and implementation.

You will assist in the delivery of continuous improvement, behavioural change and developing a culture conducive to performance outcomes.

Your ability to encourage and mentor continued compliance to the company minimum standards and seek ownership from site employees is critical to the success of your role.


Please send your current resume with an application letter to: nia.lloyd@catercareservices.com.au]]></AdDetails>
						      <ApplicationEmail>leon@catercareservices.com.au</ApplicationEmail>
						      <ApplicationURL>http://www.catercare.com.au/career/?jobid=61243000000233013</ApplicationURL>
						      <ResidentsOnly>Yes</ResidentsOnly>
						      <Items>
						        <Item Name="Jobtitle">SHE Advisor</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant">NIA LLOYD (1210LLON)</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Email">leon@catercareservices.com.au</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Telephone">1300 658 700</Item>
						        <Item Name="RefNumber">61243000000233013</Item>
						      </Items>
						      <Listing MarketSegments="Main">
							        <Classification Name="Location">MackayCoalfields</Classification>
							        <Classification Name="Area"></Classification>
							        <Classification Name="WorkType">FullTime</Classification>
							       	<Classification Name="Classification">HospitalityTourism</Classification>
						        	<Classification Name="SubClassification">HospitalTourismManagement</Classification>					      
						      </Listing>
						      <Salary Type="AnnualPackage" Min="60000" Max="79999" AdditionalText="" />
						      <StandOut IsStandOut="false" LogoID="172084" Bullet1="" Bullet2="" Bullet3="" />
						    </Job>
						<Job Reference="61243000000228661" TemplateID="83291" ScreenID="">
						      <Title>Expression of Interest - Site Manager</Title>
						      <SearchTitle>Expression of Interest - Site Manager</SearchTitle>
						      <Description>Cater Care Services specialises in providing facility support services to the Mining, Construction, Off-Shore and Defence Industries</Description>
						      <AdDetails><![CDATA[Cater Care Services specialises in providing facility support services to the Mining, Construction, Off-Shore and Defence Industries through Australia and Overseas.  We are currently seeking Expressions of Interest for a Relief Site Manager to work at various sites throughout Australia.

The Site Manager role will be responsible for:

Managing the daily requirements of your site, ensuring all service requirements are delivered in accordance with Company standards and client expectations.

The successful applicant will have the following skills or experience:

<br />•	A passion for  excellent customer skills with the ability to be flexible and be able to plan site management requirements in advance
<br />•	Motivated and accountable
<br />•	5 years relevant industry experience
<br />•	Demonstrated experience in Safety and HACCP
<br />•	People management experience
<br />•	Business financials understanding
<br />•	Ability to operate a site within budget requirements
<br />•	Demonstrated experience with key components of the role

<br /> You will be required to motivate and educate and lead your team to produce service quality of high standards, keep staff turnover to a minimum and customer satisfaction at high levels and operate your site in a profitable operation.  You will be prepared to undertake duties of other roles on site to maintain the company’s commitment to contractual service requirements.   

Your duties will include:

<br />•	Staff training and development
<br />•	Staff management
<br />•	Administration paper work
<br />•	Accommodation System management
<br />•	Stock control, ordering and stocktakes
<br />•	Cash handling and banking and reconciliation
<br />•	Rostering
<br />•	Client Relationship Management

<br /> Experience with a similar role in a camp environment will be highly regarded. This is a FIFO role from Brisbane, working a 2 week on 1 week off roster.

<br />•	Current references required at the interview
<br />•	A medical will be required

<br /> To apply for this position please send an Application Letter together with a resume to nia.lloyd@catercareservices.com.au]]></AdDetails>
						      <ApplicationEmail>leon@catercareservices.com.au</ApplicationEmail>
						      <ApplicationURL>http://www.catercare.com.au/career/?jobid=61243000000228661</ApplicationURL>
						      <ResidentsOnly>Yes</ResidentsOnly>
						      <Items>
						        <Item Name="Jobtitle">Expression of Interest - Site Manager</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant">NIA LLOYD (1210LLON)</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Email">leon@catercareservices.com.au</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Telephone">1300 658 700</Item>
						        <Item Name="RefNumber">61243000000228661</Item>
						      </Items>
						      <Listing MarketSegments="Main">
							        <Classification Name="Location">Brisbane</Classification>
							        <Classification Name="Area"></Classification>
							        <Classification Name="WorkType">FullTime</Classification>
							       	<Classification Name="Classification">HospitalityTourism</Classification>
						        	<Classification Name="SubClassification">HospitalTourismManagement</Classification>					      
						      </Listing>
						      <Salary Type="AnnualPackage" Min="60000" Max="79999" AdditionalText="" />
						      <StandOut IsStandOut="false" LogoID="172084" Bullet1="" Bullet2="" Bullet3="" />
						    </Job>
						<Job Reference="61243000000230035" TemplateID="83291" ScreenID="">
						      <Title>Chef</Title>
						      <SearchTitle>Chef</SearchTitle>
						      <Description>Cater Care Services specialises in the provision of catering and accommodation services to the mining industry.</Description>
						      <AdDetails><![CDATA[Cater Care Services specialises in the provision of catering and accommodation services to the mining industry.

Due to continued growth in WA, Cater Care Services have a requirement for a experienced Chef.

The positions are DIDO from Perth on a 2 week on 1 week off roster and a competitive salary to match experience and roster.

The ideal candidate will demonstrate the following: 
<br />•A personal belief in a safety first culture
<br />•Exceptional customer service skills
<br />•Chef Qualifications
<br />•Be a team player with a &quot;can do&quot; attitude



Details of two current referees must be provided at the interview.

To apply for this position please send your current resume to : hradminwa@catercareservices.com.au]]></AdDetails>
						      <ApplicationEmail>leon@catercareservices.com.au</ApplicationEmail>
						      <ApplicationURL>http://www.catercare.com.au/career/?jobid=61243000000230035</ApplicationURL>
						      <ResidentsOnly>Yes</ResidentsOnly>
						      <Items>
						        <Item Name="Jobtitle">Chef</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant">GARVIN BRADNAM (1158BRAG)</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Email">leon@catercareservices.com.au</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Telephone">1300 658 700</Item>
						        <Item Name="RefNumber">61243000000230035</Item>
						      </Items>
						      <Listing MarketSegments="Main">
							        <Classification Name="Location">GeraldtonGascoyneMidwest</Classification>
							        <Classification Name="Area"></Classification>
							        <Classification Name="WorkType">FullTime</Classification>
							       	<Classification Name="Classification">HospitalityTourism</Classification>
						        	<Classification Name="SubClassification">Chefs/Cooks</Classification>					      
						      </Listing>
						      <Salary Type="AnnualPackage" Min="60000" Max="79999" AdditionalText="" />
						      <StandOut IsStandOut="false" LogoID="172084" Bullet1="" Bullet2="" Bullet3="" />
						    </Job>
						<Job Reference="61243000000230001" TemplateID="83291" ScreenID="">
						      <Title>Junior Administration Assistant</Title>
						      <SearchTitle>Junior Administration Assistant</SearchTitle>
						      <Description>Cater Care Group is a rapidly growing organisation providing catering and accommodation services within a diverse range of contracts throughout Australia, and offshore.</Description>
						      <AdDetails><![CDATA[<br />•	Rapidly Growing Organisation
<br />•	Full Time, Monday to Friday
<br />•	Parramatta Location

<br />Cater Care Group is a rapidly growing organisation providing catering and accommodation services within a diverse range of contracts throughout Australia, and offshore.

We are currently seeking the services for a Junior Administrative Assistant for our Sydney Office located in Parramatta.

Duties will include:  Reception, Mailing, Banking, Typing Correspondence, Organising Couriers and General Office Duties.

The successful applicant will have the ability to touch type and knowledge of the Microsoft Office package.  

Accuracy and attention to detail is highly regarded along with a friendly and accommodating attitude.

To apply for this position please send a covering letter with your resume to: sydadmin@catercareaustralia.com.au]]></AdDetails>
						      <ApplicationEmail>leon@catercareservices.com.au</ApplicationEmail>
						      <ApplicationURL>http://www.catercare.com.au/career/?jobid=61243000000230001</ApplicationURL>
						      <ResidentsOnly>Yes</ResidentsOnly>
						      <Items>
						        <Item Name="Jobtitle">Junior Administration Assistant</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant">PETA MCDONNELL (0573MCDP)</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Email">leon@catercareservices.com.au</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Telephone">1300 658 700</Item>
						        <Item Name="RefNumber">61243000000230001</Item>
						      </Items>
						      <Listing MarketSegments="Main">
							        <Classification Name="Location">Sydney</Classification>
							        <Classification Name="Area"></Classification>
							        <Classification Name="WorkType">FullTime</Classification>
							       	<Classification Name="Classification">HospitalityTourism</Classification>
						        	<Classification Name="SubClassification">HospitalTourismManagement</Classification>					      
						      </Listing>
						      <Salary Type="AnnualPackage" Min="1" Max="39999" AdditionalText="" />
						      <StandOut IsStandOut="false" LogoID="172084" Bullet1="" Bullet2="" Bullet3="" />
						    </Job>
						<Job Reference="61243000000230009" TemplateID="83291" ScreenID="">
						      <Title>Senior Administration Assistant</Title>
						      <SearchTitle>Senior Administration Assistant</SearchTitle>
						      <Description>Cater Care Group is a rapidly growing organisation providing catering and accommodation services within a diverse range of contracts throughout Australia, and offshore.</Description>
						      <AdDetails><![CDATA[<br />•	Rapidly Growing Organisation
<br />•	Career Opportunity
<br />•	Parramatta Location

<br />Cater Care Group is a rapidly growing organisation providing catering and accommodation services within a diverse range of contracts throughout Australia, and offshore.

We are currently seeking the services of an experienced Executive Assistant to support our Senior Management team based in our Sydney Office, Parramatta.

The ideal candidate will have a minimum of 3 years experience in a similar role, can work autonomously and be responsible for the delivery outcomes required for this position.  

The role is challenging and diverse and is an opportunity for a person wanting to expand on their current experience.
Applicants must have the following skills and experience:

<br />•	Ability to touch type at 50 wpm minimum
<br />•	An advanced understanding of the Microsoft Office Suite
<br />•	Excellent communication skills both verbal and written
<br />•	Excellent customer service skills
<br />•	Flexibility in challenging situations
<br />•	Strong Time Management skills

<br />Demonstrated experience in a similar role in a contract catering environment would be highly regarded.

To apply for this position please send a covering letter and resume to:  sydadmin@catercareaustralia.com.au]]></AdDetails>
						      <ApplicationEmail>leon@catercareservices.com.au</ApplicationEmail>
						      <ApplicationURL>http://www.catercare.com.au/career/?jobid=61243000000230009</ApplicationURL>
						      <ResidentsOnly>Yes</ResidentsOnly>
						      <Items>
						        <Item Name="Jobtitle">Senior Administration Assistant</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant">PETA MCDONNELL (0573MCDP)</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Email">leon@catercareservices.com.au</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Telephone">1300 658 700</Item>
						        <Item Name="RefNumber">61243000000230009</Item>
						      </Items>
						      <Listing MarketSegments="Main">
							        <Classification Name="Location">Sydney</Classification>
							        <Classification Name="Area"></Classification>
							        <Classification Name="WorkType">FullTime</Classification>
							       	<Classification Name="Classification">HospitalityTourism</Classification>
						        	<Classification Name="SubClassification">HospitalTourismManagement</Classification>					      
						      </Listing>
						      <Salary Type="AnnualPackage" Min="40000" Max="59999" AdditionalText="" />
						      <StandOut IsStandOut="false" LogoID="172084" Bullet1="" Bullet2="" Bullet3="" />
						    </Job>
						<Job Reference="61243000000226381" TemplateID="83291" ScreenID="">
						      <Title>Expression of Interest - Chef</Title>
						      <SearchTitle>Expression of Interest - Chef</SearchTitle>
						      <Description>Cater Care Services specialises in providing facility support services to the Mining, Construction, Off-Shore and Defence Industries</Description>
						      <AdDetails><![CDATA[Cater Care Services specialises in providing facility support services to the Mining, Construction, Off-Shore and Defence Industries through Australia and Overseas.  We are currently seeking Expressions of Interest for Chefs in Northern Territory.

As Chef you will be responsible for ensuring effective operation of the food preparation, production and service requirements of the site.

The successful applicant will have the following skills or experience:

<br />•	A passion for  excellent customer skills with the ability to be flexible and be able to plan residents’ catering requirements in advance
<br />•	Motivated and accountable
<br />•	Trade qualifications
<br />•	3 years relevant industry experience
<br />•	Demonstrated experience in Safety and HACCP
<br />•	Excellent organisational skills

<br /> You will be required to adhere to all standards as set by the Company, and you will have strong work ethics combined with time management skills and be prepared to assist all other employee in maintaining schedules and service commitments when required.

Experience with a similar role in a camp environment will be highly regarded.

This is a Drive In/Drive Out role only with a 2 weeks on 1 week off roster. 

<br />•	Current references required at the interview
<br />•	A medical will be required

<br /> To apply for this position please send an Application Letter together with a resume to nia.lloyd@catercareservices.com.au]]></AdDetails>
						      <ApplicationEmail>leon@catercareservices.com.au</ApplicationEmail>
						      <ApplicationURL>http://www.catercare.com.au/career/?jobid=61243000000226381</ApplicationURL>
						      <ResidentsOnly>Yes</ResidentsOnly>
						      <Items>
						        <Item Name="Jobtitle">Expression of Interest - Chef</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant">NIA LLOYD (1210LLON)</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Email">leon@catercareservices.com.au</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Telephone">1300 658 700</Item>
						        <Item Name="RefNumber">61243000000226381</Item>
						      </Items>
						      <Listing MarketSegments="Main">
							        <Classification Name="Location">Darwin</Classification>
							        <Classification Name="Area"></Classification>
							        <Classification Name="WorkType">FullTime</Classification>
							       	<Classification Name="Classification">HospitalityTourism</Classification>
						        	<Classification Name="SubClassification">Chefs/Cooks</Classification>					      
						      </Listing>
						      <Salary Type="AnnualPackage" Min="60000" Max="79999" AdditionalText="" />
						      <StandOut IsStandOut="false" LogoID="172084" Bullet1="" Bullet2="" Bullet3="" />
						    </Job>
						<Job Reference="61243000000224015" TemplateID="83291" ScreenID="">
						      <Title>Commis Chef</Title>
						      <SearchTitle>Commis Chef</SearchTitle>
						      <Description>Cater Care Australia specialises in providing catering services to sectors such as Retail – Coffee Shops, Health &amp; Juice Bars, Business &amp; Industry – Industrial Canteens, Healthcare – Nursing Homes, Retirement Villages and Education – Private Schools, Universities and TAFE Colleges.  Our core values of Care, Pride &amp; Community are values that our people own and believe in, and demonstrate throughout all aspects of our business, on a daily basis.</Description>
						      <AdDetails><![CDATA[Cater Care Australia specialises in providing catering services to sectors such as Retail – Coffee Shops, Health &amp; Juice Bars, Business &amp; Industry – Industrial Canteens, Healthcare – Nursing Homes, Retirement Villages and Education – Private Schools, Universities and TAFE Colleges.  Our core values of Care, Pride &amp; Community are values that our people own and believe in, and demonstrate throughout all aspects of our business, on a daily basis.

<br />•	North Sydney
<br />•	Full Time and Casual Position available
<br />•	Career Growth Opportunities

<br />We are currently seeking the services of a Commis Chef to be part of our site team based in North Sydney.  The Commis Chef will be responsible for catering to 39 students at a private boarding school, delivering high quality functions, high customer service standards and stock control.  The roster will be Monday to Friday 11.30am to 7.30pm and Saturday 3.30pm to 7.30pm.

The successful applicant will have the following skills and experience:
<br />•	Trade qualified
<br />•	Function experience
<br />•	Ability to work unsupervised
<br />•	Ability to think on your feet
<br />•	Knowledge of food safety systems
<br />•	Reliable
<br />•	Excellent communication skills

<br />This position offers great growth prospects to the right candidate within a national company.  To apply for this position please send a resume to Geoff@catercareaustralia.com.au]]></AdDetails>
						      <ApplicationEmail>leon@catercareservices.com.au</ApplicationEmail>
						      <ApplicationURL>http://www.catercare.com.au/career/?jobid=61243000000224015</ApplicationURL>
						      <ResidentsOnly>Yes</ResidentsOnly>
						      <Items>
						        <Item Name="Jobtitle">Commis Chef</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant">PETA MCDONNELL (0573MCDP)</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Email">leon@catercareservices.com.au</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Telephone">1300 658 700</Item>
						        <Item Name="RefNumber">61243000000224015</Item>
						      </Items>
						      <Listing MarketSegments="Main">
							        <Classification Name="Location">Sydney</Classification>
							        <Classification Name="Area"></Classification>
							        <Classification Name="WorkType">FullTime</Classification>
							       	<Classification Name="Classification">HospitalityTourism</Classification>
						        	<Classification Name="SubClassification">HospitalTourismManagement</Classification>					      
						      </Listing>
						      <Salary Type="AnnualPackage" Min="1" Max="39999" AdditionalText="" />
						      <StandOut IsStandOut="false" LogoID="172084" Bullet1="" Bullet2="" Bullet3="" />
						    </Job>
						<Job Reference="61243000000215435" TemplateID="83291" ScreenID="">
						      <Title>Expression of Interest - Chef</Title>
						      <SearchTitle>Expression of Interest - Chef</SearchTitle>
						      <Description>Cater Care Services specialises in providing facility support services to the Mining, Construction, Off-Shore and Defence Industries</Description>
						      <AdDetails><![CDATA[Cater Care Services specialises in providing facility support services to the Mining, Construction, Off-Shore and Defence Industries through Australia and Overseas.  We are currently seeking the services of Expressions of Interest for Chefs for various positions within Australia.

As Chef you will be responsible for ensuring effective operation of the food preparation, production and service requirements of the site.

The successful applicant will have the following skills or experience:

<br />•	A passion for  excellent customer skills with the ability to be flexible and be able to plan residents’ catering requirements in advance
<br />•	Motivated and accountable
<br />•	Trade qualifications
<br />•	3 years relevant industry experience
<br />•	Demonstrated experience in Safety and HACCP
<br />•	Excellent organisational skills

<br /> You will be required to adhere to all standards as set by the Company, and you will have strong work ethics combined with time management skills and be prepared to assist all other employee in maintaining schedules and service commitments when required.

Experience with a similar role in a camp environment will be highly regarded.

<br />•	Current references required at the interview
<br />•	A medical will be required

<br /> To apply for this position please send an Application Letter together with a resume to nia.lloyd@catercareservices.com.au]]></AdDetails>
						      <ApplicationEmail>leon@catercareservices.com.au</ApplicationEmail>
						      <ApplicationURL>http://www.catercare.com.au/career/?jobid=61243000000215435</ApplicationURL>
						      <ResidentsOnly>Yes</ResidentsOnly>
						      <Items>
						        <Item Name="Jobtitle">Expression of Interest - Chef</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant">NIA LLOYD (1210LLON)</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Email">leon@catercareservices.com.au</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Telephone">1300 658 700</Item>
						        <Item Name="RefNumber">61243000000215435</Item>
						      </Items>
						      <Listing MarketSegments="Main">
							        <Classification Name="Location">Brisbane</Classification>
							        <Classification Name="Area"></Classification>
							        <Classification Name="WorkType">FullTime</Classification>
							       	<Classification Name="Classification">HospitalityTourism</Classification>
						        	<Classification Name="SubClassification">Chefs/Cooks</Classification>					      
						      </Listing>
						      <Salary Type="AnnualPackage" Min="60000" Max="79999" AdditionalText="" />
						      <StandOut IsStandOut="false" LogoID="172084" Bullet1="" Bullet2="" Bullet3="" />
						    </Job>
						<Job Reference="61243000000218277" TemplateID="83291" ScreenID="">
						      <Title>Head Chef</Title>
						      <SearchTitle>Head Chef</SearchTitle>
						      <Description>Cater Care Services specialises in the provision of catering and accommodation services to the construction and mining industries.  Due to continued growth in Western Australia, Cater Care Services has a vacancy for a Head Chef on one of our remote sites.</Description>
						      <AdDetails><![CDATA[Cater Care Services specialises in the provision of catering and accommodation services to the construction and mining industries.  Due to continued growth in Western Australia, Cater Care Services has a vacancy for a Head Chef on one of our remote sites.

<br />•	FIFO Roster
<br />•	Competitive Salary
<br />•	Hands On Role

<br />This position is FIFO from Perth, 2 weeks on &amp; 1 week off with a competitive salary to match experience.

The ideal candidate will demonstrate the following:

<br />•	Leadership Skills
<br />•	The Highest customer service skills
<br />•	Remote Site experience
<br />•	Food Safety Supervisor Qualifications
<br />•	Good understanding of Safety in the workplace
<br />•	Chef Qualifications

<br />To apply for this position please send your current resume to:   hradminwa@catercareservices.com.au]]></AdDetails>
						      <ApplicationEmail>leon@catercareservices.com.au</ApplicationEmail>
						      <ApplicationURL>http://www.catercare.com.au/career/?jobid=61243000000218277</ApplicationURL>
						      <ResidentsOnly>Yes</ResidentsOnly>
						      <Items>
						        <Item Name="Jobtitle">Head Chef</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant">GARVIN BRADNAM (1158BRAG)</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Email">leon@catercareservices.com.au</Item>
						        <Item Name="Consultant Telephone">1300 658 700</Item>
						        <Item Name="RefNumber">61243000000218277</Item>
						      </Items>
						      <Listing MarketSegments="Main">
							        <Classification Name="Location">GeraldtonGascoyneMidwest</Classification>
							        <Classification Name="Area"></Classification>
							        <Classification Name="WorkType">FullTime</Classification>
							       	<Classification Name="Classification">HospitalityTourism</Classification>
						        	<Classification Name="SubClassification">Chefs/Cooks</Classification>					      
						      </Listing>
						      <Salary Type="AnnualPackage" Min="60000" Max="79999" AdditionalText="" />
						      <StandOut IsStandOut="false" LogoID="172084" Bullet1="" Bullet2="" Bullet3="" />
						    </Job>
						</Client>
					</FastLanePlus>