<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><FastLanePlus UploaderID="" AgentID="" Version="3.0">
					  <Client ID="" MinJobs="0" MaxJobs="9999999"><Job Reference="61243000000152003" TemplateID="" ScreenID="">
					      <Title>WA Business Development Manager</Title>
					      <SearchTitle>WA Business Development Manager</SearchTitle>
					      <Description>Cater Care specialises in providing facility support services to the Mining, Construction, Off-Shore &amp; Defence Industries throughout Australasia</Description>
					      <AdDetails><![CDATA[<p>We are currently seeking the services of an experienced Business Development Manager.

The Business Development Manager will be responsible for:

•	Follow the strategic plans of the assigned area specifically the annual plans and objectives
•	Build and maintain client relationships (current and future).
•	Expand brand awareness. 
•	Be responsible for the collection and management of local data and other market intelligence for the Business Development department to ensure through and competitive positioning of the company. 
•	Ensure thorough, planned, structured and timely research is conducted.
•	Be accountable for managing the timely receipt and despatch (if local) of requests for proposal and other opportunities.
•	Ensure the Business Development working initiative and processes are consistent in the assigned area.
•	Prepare progress and summary reports and assist in business planning. 
•	Be accountable for ensuring sales and budget targets assigned in your areas are managed and achieved as a minimum. 
•	Establish an in depth and updated study of target business sectors, clients, synergies and future prospects and potential initiatives for development.
•	Assist in the preparation of feasibility studies and subject opportunity papers as required in the assigned areas. 
•	Identify specific project leads and manage the introduction and follow through with summary, selection and strategy papers 


The successful applicant will have the following skills or experience:

•	At least 5 years’ experience in a similar role within a catering organisation
•	High level of organisation
•	Clear and concise communicator

Working with Cater Care provides an opportunity to work with Australia&#39;s largest privately owned facilities management company. Coupled with an excellent benefits package, this is a fantastic opportunity for a motivated and enthusiastic professional.

To apply for this position please send an Application Letter together with a resume to nia.lloyd@catercareservices.com.au]</p>]]></AdDetails>
					      <ApplicationEmail>leon@catercareservices.com.au</ApplicationEmail>
					      <ApplicationURL>No</ApplicationURL>
					      <ResidentsOnly>Yes</ResidentsOnly>
					      <Items>
					        <Item Name="Jobtitle">WA Business Development Manager</Item>
					        <Item Name="Consultant">Leon Hayes (0001)</Item>
					        <Item Name="Consultant Email">leon@catercareservices.com.au</Item>
					        <Item Name="Consultant Telephone">1300 658 700</Item>
					        <Item Name="RefNumber">61243000000152003</Item>
					      </Items>
					      <Listing MarketSegments="Main">
						        <Classification Name="Location">Sydney</Classification>
						        <Classification Name="Area"></Classification>
						        <Classification Name="WorkType">Full time</Classification>
						       	<Classification Name="Classification">HospitalityTourism</Classification>
					        	<Classification Name="SubClassification">HospitalTourismManagement</Classification>					      
					      </Listing>
					      <Salary Type="AnnualPackage" Min="60000" Max="79999" AdditionalText="Not applicable" />
					      <StandOut IsStandOut="true" LogoID="" Bullet1="Experienced and Motivated Business Development Manager" Bullet2="Opportunity to work within Australia&#39;s Resource &amp; Mining Sector" Bullet3="Opportunity for interstate &amp; overseas travel" />
					    </Job>
					</Client>
					</FastLanePlus>